Contact

1912.jaimehta@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jaimehta-9860ab1aa (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Graphic Design

Jai Mehta

Web developer , Graphic designer Haryana

Summary

Experienced Graphic Designer with a demonstrated knowledge in the design industry. Skilled in Adobe Indesign CC, Graphic Design, Full-Stack Development, Page Layout, and HTML. Strong arts and design professional with a Btech cse focused in artificial intelligence from CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY.

Experience

Freelance
Graphic Designer
June 2020 - Present (3 months)
Chandigarh, India

Freelance
Frontend Developer
June 2020 - June 2020 (1 month)

Education

CHANDIGARH UNIVERSITY

Btech cse, artificial intelligence · (2019 - 2023)

baba banda bahadur public school school academics, class 10th academics · (2015 - 2016)

CSS School

12, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates